A Guide to the Samuel M. Janney Papers, 1790-1922
Library of Virginia
- Phineas Janney Mercantile Accounts, 18901-1891 (Folder 29)
  - Accounts, 1890-1891 (Folder 29)
    - Account, 23 May 1890, with E. J. Miller and Son of Alexandria, Virginia., f; 1 leaf
    - Account, 28 May 1890, with William T. Dixon and Brother of Baltimore, Maryland., g; 1 leaf
    - Account, 10 December 1890, with Henry Sonneborn and Company of Baltimore, Maryland., h; 1 leaf
    - Account, 25 April 1891, with Joel J. Baily and Company of Philadelphia, Pennsylvania., i; 4 pages
    - Account, 17 October 1891, with William T. Dixon and Brother of Baltimore, Maryland., j; 1 leaf
    - Account, 28 October 1891, with A. S. Bates, agent for R. A. Paxton of Waterford, Virginia., k; 1 leaf
- Samuel M. Janney Account Books, Daybooks, Memorandum Books, 1836-1870
  - S. M. Janney Cotton Factory, Occoquan, Virginia, Daybook, 27 July 1836-10 March 1841
  - S. M. Janney, Executor's and Trustee's Accounts, 1841-1858
  - Phineas Janney General Store, Alexandria, Virginia, Daybook, 17 May 1848-17 May 1854
  - Farmers Bank of Virginia, Alexandria Branch, in account with Phineas Janney's Executors, 1852-1860
  - Cash Account Book, 1850-1858
  - John Janney General Store, Goose Creek, Virginia, Ledger; S. M. Janney and Company General Store, Goose Creek, Virginia, Ledger 1854-1857, 1859-1860
  - S. M. Janney and Company General Store, Goose Creek, Virginia, Daybook 21 July 1856-6 February 1861
  - S. M. Janney and Company General Store, Goose Creek, Virginia, Daybook 19 March 1861-9 July 1869
  - William Tate Account Book, 1840-1860
  - William Tate Memorandum Book, 1840-1870